[Music]
[音乐]
okay good morning thank you for coming
好的，早上好，谢谢你的光临
thank you for your patience while we
谢谢您在我们期间的耐心配合
dealt with various technical
处理各种技术
difficulties it's always a it's always
困难永远是永远
amusing and at least under entertaining
有趣，至少在娱乐性方面
to give a talk that involves three
进行涉及三个方面的演讲
laptops to laptops I've lost count
笔记本电脑到我已经数不清的笔记本电脑
myself all right so this talk is a bit
我自己很好，所以这个话题有点
about Java today but it's also an
关于Java的今天，但这也是
attempt to peer into the future to try
尝试凝视未来
to see what's coming down the road I
看看接下来会发生什么
will do lots of well several several
会做很多好几个
demos I'll probably miss type something
演示，我可能会错过键入内容
if you see me make a mistake please
如果你看到我做错了，请
PLEASE shout out to correct me and help
请大喊大叫来纠正我并提供帮助
me out up here questions are ok during
我在这里，问题还可以
the demos but this isn't this isn't
演示，但这不是，不是
meant to be a QA at least until the end
至少要进行质量检查
we have time it's a good time at the end
我们有时间，这是个好时机
happy to take questions there I would
我很乐意在那里提问
like to start with the canonical set of
喜欢从规范的一组开始
polls how many people are using Java 8
调查多少人正在使用Java 8
in production how many people people are
生产中有多少人
using Java 11 in production yeah good
在生产中使用Java 11是的，很好
how many people are at least using using
至少有多少人正在使用
a release later than 8 in development
开发中的版本晚于8
trying it out kicking the tires how many
尝试踢轮胎多少
people have downloaded Java 12 and are
人们已经下载了Java 12，并且
doing something with it ok that that's
用它做某事，那是
that's that's pretty good by the end of
到年底，那是相当不错的
this I hope to convince more of you to
我希望这能说服更多的人
go and do that even if you don't use it
即使不使用也去做
in production you know at the very least
在生产中你至少知道
download 12 even download 13 and try it
下载12甚至下载13并尝试
out and send this feedback on some of
并发送有关一些反馈
the new features alright before we look
新功能好在我们看之前
at specific features
在特定功能
let's first kind of just remind
让我们先提醒一下
ourselves a bit how is it that we decide
我们自己怎么决定
to add add things to Java do we just add
向Java添加东西我们只是添加
stuff to keep up with the cool kids or
跟酷孩子在一起的东西
you know add stuff to keep it keep it
你知道添加东西以保持它
appealing no matter what and no of
无论什么都不吸引
course not what does Drive Java forward
当然不是什么推动Java向前发展
for almost 24 years Java has been driven
Java已经被驱动了将近24年
by by two big goals that's 24 they'll be
通过两个24岁的大目标，他们将
24 years on the 20
20年的24年
third of this month by the way two big
顺便说一句本月三号
goals the first is developer
目标第一是开发者
productivity Java is about helping
生产力Java旨在帮助
developers build and maintain large and
开发人员建立并维护大型和
reliable programs yes sometimes people
可靠的程序是有时人们
complain that the language is a bit
抱怨语言有点
verbose but that verbosity to an extent
冗长但一定程度的冗长
has an advantage because it means the
有一个优势，因为这意味着
code that you write today you will be
您今天编写的代码将是
able to understand a year from now you
一年后就能了解你
know somebody you you've never met will
知道你从未见过的人会
be able to understand that ten twenty
能够理解十点二十
years from now Java isn't about writing
从现在开始Java不再是关于编写
one-off scripts it never it never has
永无止境的一次性脚本
been is about building things for the
一直在为建造东西
long haul being able to maintain them
长期维持他们的能力
for the long haul the other big goal for
从长远来看，另一个大目标是
24 years has been programmed performance
已设定24年的性能
performance of course we measure in many
我们当然会在许多方面衡量绩效
different ways we measure time in in the
我们测量时间的不同方式
form of startup time and latency and
启动时间和延迟的形式以及
throughput we measure space both static
吞吐量我们测量空间既是静态的
space of a system in storage of dinah of
系统的存储空间
a dynamic space in terms of memory
就记忆而言的动态空间
consumption we might we measure
我们可能测量的消费
scalability in a bunch of ways we you
我们为您提供多种扩展性
know we like to talk about you know java
知道我们喜欢谈论你知道Java
working from iphones it's a big iron and
在iPhone上工作是很大的麻烦
actually making that a real thing which
真正使那个成为现实
well it kind of is for almost 24 years
差不多有24年了
we've pursued these two big goals in the
我们已经在
face of constantly evolving factors and
面对不断变化的因素
this is part of what makes working on
这是使工作得以进行的一部分
Java itself fun that's awesome what
Java本身的有趣之处
makes working on it a real challenge
使它成为一个真正的挑战
from time to time things that things are
不时的事物
always changing programming paradigms
总是在改变编程范例
are changing people are more interested
正在改变的人更感兴趣
now in mixed functional and
现在混合功能和
object-oriented programming data
面向对象的编程数据
oriented programming is becoming a thing
面向程序设计正在成为一件事
application areas are changing we have
应用领域正在发生变化
you know big data and machine learning
你知道大数据和机器学习
which a lot of people want to do in Java
很多人想用Java做的事情
but Java isn't doing as well for them as
但是Java对他们来说不如
it could so we're working on ways to
可以，所以我们正在研究
make that better
使它变得更好
deployment styles are changing you know
部署样式正在改变，您知道
we used to talk about about jar files
我们曾经谈论过jar文件
you know lately it loaded into web
你知道最近它加载到网络
browsers and security managers and and
浏览器和安全管理器以及
all this other stuff but guess what job
所有其他的东西，但猜猜做什么
Java apps and web browser are not a
Java应用程序和Web浏览器不是
thing in in this decade of this century
在这个世纪的这个十年中的事情
but Java is being used to deploy
但是Java被用来部署
applications in clouds into and you
云中的应用程序和您
publish the pack
发布包
in the packaged applications to wind up
在打包的应用程序中结束
in the in app stores and things like
在应用商店中
that and of course hardware is all is
那当然是硬件
always evolving we now have machines
不断发展，我们现在拥有机器
with terabyte memories we have a deeper
拥有TB级的记忆，我们可以更深入地了解
memory memory hierarchies within lots of
内存层次结构
caches between your processor core and
在您的处理器核心和
your memory system we have deeper and
您的存储系统，我们有更深
more numerous processor pipelines and we
更多的处理器管线，我们
have vector and cyndi instruction sets
具有向量和cyndi指令集
both on sort of what are now considered
两者都在考虑什么
normal processors and then they're
普通处理器，然后
really souped up ones that you find in
真的让你在里面找到了
GPUs so we're pursuing these these two
GPU，因此我们追求这两个
big goals in in light of all these
鉴于所有这些大目标
factors in some of the major active
一些主要活跃因素
projects in the open JDK community and
JDK开放社区中的项目以及
that's what I'd like to talk about it's
这就是我想谈的
a day so the ones I will discuss are
一天，所以我要讨论的是
amber which is about right sizing
琥珀色，这是正确尺寸的
language ceremony reducing some of that
语言仪式减少了一些
boilerplate you know in in effect this
您实际上知道的样板
is being led by Brian gets loom bringing
由布莱恩领导带织机带来
continuations and fibers to the Java
Java的延续和纤维
platform this is being led by Ron
由Ron领导的平台
Pressler Panama a new foreign function
Pressler Panama具有新的对外功能
and foreign data interface being led by
和外部数据接口由
Mauricio jamaat amore
毛里西奥·贾马特·爱茉莉
and finally Valhalla the big one value
最后是瓦尔哈拉最大的价值
types and specialized generics for the
的类型和专用泛型
Java platform being co-led by John Rose
Java平台由John Rose共同领导
and Brian guts so let's start with amber
和Brian胆量，所以让我们从琥珀开始
so Amber's is aimed squarely at the pain
所以琥珀的目的是针对疼痛
point that Java requires too much
指出Java需要太多
ceremony there's it there's just too
仪式那里也有
much boilerplate how many did people
多少样板
like the amount of boilerplate in Java
就像Java中的样板数量
one two okay look your your the humor
一两个好看你的幽默
guy of course you you know and this just
当然你知道的家伙，这只是
gets especially painful when you're
当你变得特别痛苦
trying to do you know micro services
试图让你知道微服务
they're just gonna exchange them data in
他们只是要交换数据
and out and you have to deal with all
出来，你必须处理所有
these for those classes and about just
这些用于那些课程，大约
just just why let's make it better
只是为什么让我们变得更好
so the amber solution is actually it's
所以琥珀色的解决方案实际上是
not we're not attacking boilerplate
不，我们不是在攻击样板
directly right we could attack
就可以攻击
boilerplate directly by transferring the
通过转移
Java syntax into something like
Java语法变成类似
pl and then all your programs would be
请然后所有程序
really dense and compact and there would
真的很紧凑
be no boilerplate but they would also be
没有样板，但他们也将
unmaintainable rather the approach we're
难以维持，而是我们所采用的方法
taking is creating a series of language
接受正在创造一系列语言
features over time they delivered over
随着时间的推移，它们交付的功能
time they work together that let you
他们在一起的时间让你
express more clearly what you mean and
更清楚地表达你的意思，
if you can express more clearly what you
如果你能更清楚地表达你的意思
mean then the boilerplate will take care
这意味着样板会注意
of itself
本身
there will be less of it there will
那里会更少
still be a little bit probably because
仍然有点可能是因为
that's just the way Java is all right
这就是Java没问题的方式
how many people were interested Tricia's
有多少人对特里西娅的感兴趣
talked just before this one okay I
在此之前就聊了
couldn't be here so I'll ask you and
不可能在这里，所以我会问你，
I'll dynamically optimize this talk as
我将动态优化此讨论
we go did she talk about local variable
我们去找她谈论局部变量了吗
type inference yes a little bit should I
类型推断是一点我应该
talk about it yes okay fine I'll talk
说说吧，好的，我再说
about it all right type in inference
关于它可以推断类型
does Java have type inference yes no did
Java是否具有类型推断？
it always okay so a lot of people think
总是可以的，所以很多人认为
think Java doesn't have type inference
认为Java没有类型推断
or never really had it until like just
或从未真正拥有它，直到
recently or something but it's actually
最近或某事，但实际上
had type inference for a long time back
很久以前就有类型推断
in Java 5 when we did generics when we
在Java 5中，当我们做泛型时
added generics we could have made you
添加了仿制药，我们本可以使您
write the generic type of the return
编写退货的通用类型
type of every method invocation so if
每个方法调用的类型，因此如果
you want to invoke collections empty
您想将集合调用为空
list you would have to type string in
列出您必须在其中输入字符串
pointy brackets to indicate the return
尖括号指示返回
type but that would have been done so we
打字，但那样做就可以了，所以我们
didn't do that getting you know the
并没有让您知道
compiler has all the information that it
编译器拥有所有的信息
needs to determine that well you know
需要确定你知道
the string is a string is there is the
字符串是一个字符串，是否存在
return type in this case so you don't
在这种情况下返回类型，这样您就不会
have to write that you can if you want
必须写你可以的话
but I've never actually seen anyone do
但我从未真正见过任何人
that in Java 7 we introduced a thing
在Java 7中我们引入了一个东西
called the diamond operator list of
称为“钻石运营商列表”
string list equals new ArrayList string
字符串列表等于新的ArrayList字符串
here you're tight you're typing string
在这里，你很紧张，你正在输入字符串
in in pointy brackets twice well the
在尖括号中两次
compiler knows from the left-hand side
编译器从左侧知道
that this is going to be an ArrayList
这将是一个ArrayList
list of string so you could just
字符串列表，因此您可以
substitute that for you on the right
在右边代替你
hand side so you can just tie it you can
手边，所以你可以绑它就可以
just type diamond empty diamond empty
只需输入钻石空钻石空
empty empty pointy brackets so the
空的尖尖的括号，所以
compiled
已编译
we'll fill that in for you we couldn't
我们会为您填写，我们无法
infer the pointy brackets themselves
推断尖括号本身
because without the pointy brackets that
因为没有尖括号
actually has a different meaning as a
实际上与
thing called a raw type and so we're
被称为原始类型的东西，所以我们
kind of stuck with that but at least at
那种坚持，但至少在
least it got less less verbose and 7 in
至少它的冗长程度降低了7
8 when we introduced lambdas you can
8当我们引入lambda时，您可以
write a lambda like this you can write
这样写一个lambda，你可以写
the the the type of each lambda
每个lambda的类型
parameter variable in this case string s
在这种情况下，参数变量为字符串s
but you don't have to the compiler can
但您不必编译器就可以
infer it you can just just type s arrow
推断出您只需输入s箭头即可
S dot length now sometimes it is useful
点长度现在有时很有用
start to write out the type of a lambda
开始写出lambda的类型
parameter variable but you don't have to
参数变量，但您不必
more type inference in Java 10 we
Java 10中的更多类型推断
introduced local variable type inference
引入局部变量类型推断
local variable type inference is for
局部变量类型推断适用于
cases like this we've all written this
这样的情况我们都写了
code bufferedreader reader equals new
代码bufferedreader reader等于new
buffered reader okay fine and yeah sure
缓冲的读者好吧，是的
your ID can partly write that for you
您的身份证可以部分为您写
but but but come on do I really need to
但是但是来吧，我真的需要
even read buffered reader twice so in 10
甚至两次读取缓冲的读取器，所以10
we have the VAR keyword sudo it's a
我们有VAR关键字sudo，它是一个
technically it's a pseudo keyword don't
从技术上讲，这是一个伪关键字
tell anybody so you can set you you can
告诉任何人，以便您可以设置您可以
type var reader equals new buffered
类型var reader等于新缓冲
reader the compiler has enough
读者编译器已经足够
information on the right-hand side of
信息在右侧
the assignment to understand oh yeah
作业要了解哦，是的
it's a buffered reader so it inserts it
这是一个缓冲的读取器，因此将其插入
effectively inserts that on the
有效地将其插入
left-hand side so this is a it is
左侧，所以这是一个
limited to local variables that's why
限于局部变量，这就是为什么
it's called local variable type
它称为局部变量类型
inference get ahem
推论
you can't use this on fields you can't
您不能在无法使用的字段上使用
use this on method parameters or lambda
在方法参数或lambda上使用它
parameters and it's not we're not
参数，不是我们不是
turning java into JavaScript this is not
把Java变成JavaScript这不是
dynamic typing this is not saying that
动态打字这不是说
reader could be anything reader is in
读者可以是读者所在的任何人
scope here is it is going to be a
这里的范围将是一个
buffered reader for the rest of this
其余的缓冲阅读器
local variable scope no no no doubt
局部变量范围毫无疑问
about it it's it's not dynamic typing
关于它不是动态输入
like in JavaScript it's just better
就像在JavaScript中一样
stood static typing and much less
站立静态打字，少得多
keyboard typing so that's a good thing
键盘打字，所以这是一件好事
and also although it's a lot less
而且尽管它要少得多
reading for your eyes which is even
读你的眼睛，甚至
better you probably if you're in the
如果你在
habit as all admit I am of tending to
所有人都承认我有养成的习惯
use short variable names you might want
使用您可能想要的短变量名
to consider using longer ones if you
考虑使用更长的
have a
有一个
an extended example like this where
这样的扩展示例，其中
you've got a URL you were opening a
您有一个网址，正在打开一个
connection you wrap it in a scanner
连接将其包裹在扫描仪中
around it it looks much nicer with var
周围它与var看起来更好
but if I if you just used your variables
但是如果我只是用你的变量
you see an S hears and you know 20 lines
您会看到一个S听到，并且您知道20行
later your code may be less than clear
稍后您的代码可能还不清楚
so local variable type inference the VAR
所以局部变量类型推断VAR
keyword in Java 10 the details are in
Java 10中的关键字，详细信息在
jeopardy 6 if you would like to check
危险6如果您要检查
that out all right let's move on oh yeah
好的，让我们继续前进，是的
there's trip 286 let's move let's move
旅途286让我们动起来让我们动起来
on to another thing um so it's a Trish
在另一件事上，这是一个Trish
told me if she talked about switch
告诉我她是否谈论开关
expressions everybody remember it does
每个人都记得的表情
anybody want me to talk about switch
有人要我谈论开关
expressions no skip show she's got the
表情没有跳过显示她已经
same guy it sounds like the same guy
听起来像同一个人
saying yes and no here all right I'll go
说是，不是，我走了
I'll go through this quickly then
那我很快就讲完
doesn't take long alright so suppose
没多久，好吧，假设
we've got this is the week enum days of
我们有这是
the week Monday Tuesday etcetera etc and
星期一，星期二，等等等等
for the sake of this little exercise
为了这个小练习
here we want to compute the length of
在这里我们要计算的长度
the name of each day now if you're
现在，您每天的名字
clever you'll you know the clever way to
聪明的你会知道聪明的方法
do that of course is to just invoke to
这样做当然是为了
string on on a day of week object and
星期几对象上的字符串和
compute its length right but but okay
计算其长度正确但可以
what for the illustrative purposes
为了说明的目的
assume we're not going to do that
假设我们不会那样做
instead we're going to write a switch so
相反，我们要写一个开关，这样
we have a none letters variable we
我们有一个无字母的变量
switch on an add a week object we have
打开我们有一个添加一周的对象
cases Monday Friday Sunday numb letters
案件星期一星期五星期日麻木的信件
a six break Tuesday Thursday Wednesday
星期二星期三星期三休息六点
etc Wednesday on the office I think it's
等星期三在办公室，我认为是
sometimes a source of really obscure
有时是真正晦涩的来源
bugs because it is the longest name all
臭虫，因为它是最长的名字
kinds of stuff can go wrong here right
各种各样的东西可能会在这里出错
you can forget a break and and something
你可以忘记休息等等
will fall through you can forget to
会跌倒你可以忘记
assign the num letters you could you
分配数字字母你可以
could forget your default or maybe you
可能会忘记您的默认值，或者也许是您
fall into the default because you forgot
落入默认值，因为您忘记了
the break ahead of it as Brian gets like
布莱恩变得像以前一样突破
just likes to say this isn't the
只是想说这不是
language helping you out this is the
帮助您的语言是
language daring you to make a stupid
语言使你胆怯
mistake and if you think about it what
错误，如果您考虑一下
we're just computing an expression so
我们只是在计算一个表达式，所以
let's write it that way and then Java 12
让我们这样写，然后Java 12
you can you you just write you've rights
你可以，你只要写你的权利
which as an expression you can put it on
您可以将其作为一种表达方式
the right-hand side of an assignment
作业的右侧
statement you can you can embed it in a
声明，您可以将其嵌入
in a big bigger expression if you really
如果您真的以更大的表情表达
want to we borrowed the arrow syntax
要我们借用箭头语法
from lambda so that that's how you
来自lambda，所以这就是你
indicate the value of the expression and
表示表达式的值，并
as an extra special bonus the compiler
作为额外的特殊奖励，编译器
in in some cases can can see can infer
在某些情况下可以看到可以推断
can deduce that you've covered all the
可以推断出您已经涵盖了所有
cases so you don't need to provide a
案例，因此您无需提供
default if you need to provide a default
默认，如果您需要提供默认值
the compiler willow will will tell you
编译器的柳树会告诉你
and will insist that you do so but you
并会坚持要求您这样做，但您
don't have to so switch expressions are
不必这样切换表达式
in Java 12 the details are in JEP 325
在Java 12中，详细信息在JEP 325中
switch expressions are a preview feature
开关表达式是预览功能
what does this mean it means they they
这意味着什么，他们
are in the spec they're implemented by
在规范中，它们是由
the compiler so the the VM will run them
编译器，以便VM将运行它们
and everything else but they're not
和其他一切，但他们不是
enabled by default they're 99% baked but
默认情况下启用99％烘焙，但
we wanted to leverage one of these six
我们想利用这六种之一
months release cycles to get any last
数月的发布周期以获取最后的生命
feedback we can because once we add some
我们可以提供反馈，因为一旦添加了一些
to something to the language it takes
某种语言所需要的
forever to take it out you know we can
永远拿出来，你知道我们可以
sweep pretty much consider anything in
清扫几乎考虑任何东西
the language at each tin stone so if you
每块锡石的语言，如果
want to play with switch expressions in
想玩中的开关表达式
12 you need to use this command line
12您需要使用此命令行
option for both at both compile-time and
在编译时和
run-time either on the command line or
在命令行或
in your in your palm xml or whatever
在您的手掌xml中
whatever your your build system uses to
无论您的构建系统用来
enable it and if you see something funny
启用它，如果您看到有趣的东西
you have feedback for us please if I for
如果我支持，请给我们您的反馈
us please send it in because we want to
我们请发送它，因为我们想
make these final in Java 13 which is due
使这些最终在Java 13中到期
in mid-september which means we need to
在9月中旬，这意味着我们需要
be making any last decisions real soon
即将做出最后的决定
now okay let's move on to features that
现在好了，让我们继续介绍
are not yet in any early access build
尚未进行任何早期访问构建
another kind of code that we've probably
我们可能已经编写的另一种代码
all written you've got an application
都写了你有一个应用程序
you need to spew out some HTML so you
您需要喷洒一些HTML，以便您
have
有
you have some you have a string constant
你有一些你有一个字符串常量
that's basically some HTML and you wind
基本上就是一些HTML，
up writing a bunch of double quotes and
写了一堆双引号和
ending lines with pluses and quoting
用加号和引号结尾的行
things and oh yeah you've got embedded
东西，是的，你已经嵌入了
quotes inside your string constant
字符串常量内的引号
constants so don't forget to quote those
常量，所以不要忘记引用那些
with back slashes and so on and so forth
带有反斜杠等等
yeah this is kind of annoying that we
是的，这有点烦人
just have multi-line strings please yes
只有多行字符串，是的
so we're working on multi-line string
所以我们正在研究多行字符串
literals has actually been is a
字面量实际上是
surprisingly complicated feature to
令人惊讶的复杂功能
design we actually almost had them in 12
设计我们实际上几乎把它们放在12
as a preview feature but pulled them at
作为预览功能，但将其拉到
the very last minute due to valuable
由于有价值而在最后一刻
feedback that we received this is the
我们收到的反馈是
current proposal it's not in any early
目前的提议不是早
access build yet we're borrowing the
访问版本，但我们要借用
syntax may look familiar from from
语法可能看起来很像
Python and other languages a triple
Python和其他语言的三重
double quote at the beginning triple
开头三引号
double double quote at the end if you
如果您在末尾加双引号
need a triple double quote in the in in
需要in中的三重双引号
in the middle then you'll have to use a
在中间，那么您将不得不使用
bunch of back slashes but the chances of
一堆反斜杠，但有机会
that are fairly small in practice now if
现在在实践中，如果
you look at this carefully there's the
你仔细看这个
value of the string constant will
字符串常量的值将
include a bunch of whitespace from over
包括一堆空白
here that you included in order to have
您包括在这里以便拥有
your Java code be indented properly
您的Java代码正确缩进
you probably don't actually want that in
您可能实际上并不想要
your string constants so we're gonna add
您的字符串常量，所以我们要添加
a handy method to the string class
字符串类的便捷方法
called a line that will figure out what
叫了一条线，将找出
the common subsequence of leading white
白领的共同子序列
spaces and stripped out so you just get
空格和剥离，所以你就得到
the HTML and indented naturally the way
HTML并自然缩进
you expect so we're aiming that for Java
您期望如此，因此我们的目标是针对Java
13 in a JEP not quite yet written that
尚未在JEP中写成13
will also be a preview feature in 13
还将在13中成为预览功能
maybe we'll see what happens there code
也许我们会看看那里发生了什么代码
code closed for 13 is in about a month
关闭代码13大约一个月
so we'll see what happens all right
所以我们看看会发生什么
another kind of code that a lot of us
我们很多人都喜欢的另一种代码
write all the time say we have a point a
一直写，说我们有一点
point has an X and a y value we have a
点有一个X和ay值，我们有一个
constructor we have accessors is there
我们有访问器的构造函数在那里
anything missing here what's missing
这里缺少任何东西
speak up the equals hashcode into string
把等号哈希码说成字符串
oh yeah I got to write those two yeah
哦，是的，我必须写那两个
and you can do that or your ID you can
你可以做到这一点或你的ID
do it for you and and then you go and
为你做，然后你去
change it maybe a little bit but then
改变一点，也许然后
two years later you come to maintain
两年后，你来维护
this stuff then you have to go read that
这些东西，那么你必须去读
read equals hash code into string again
再次将相等的哈希码读入字符串
make sure they're there actually write
确保他们在那里实际写
all this code means well it's easy to
所有这些代码意味着很容易
cut corners and cutting corners leads to
偷工减料导致
bugs and bugs lead to unhappiness and we
虫子和虫子导致不快乐，我们
know the rest and if you look at it the
知道其余的，如果你看着它
amount of encapsulation here is actually
这里的封装量实际上是
I mean is extreme we don't need an envy
我的意思是极端，我们不需要嫉妒
encapsulation that this class is
封装此类
providing us we've got an X into y
为我们提供了X到y
they're perfectly visible there's no
他们是完全可见的，没有
reason to go to go around hiding them
去四处躲藏的理由
there's there's no secret here we just
这里没有秘密，我们只是
need a way to say this class is a
需要一种方法来说这堂课是
transparent container for some data so
一些数据的透明容器，所以
we can do that with another feature
我们可以用另一个功能做到这一点
we're working on called records
我们正在处理被叫记录
you just type record point double X
您只需输入记录点双倍X
double Y semicolon you're done that's it
双Y分号就完成了
and that stands in for all of this code
这代表了所有这些代码
that's now it's just now that that's now
那就是现在那就是现在
dimmed out records can replace all of
变暗的记录可以替换所有
that POJO code because sometimes data is
该POJO代码，因为有时数据是
just data so I have a request I'm
只是数据，所以我有一个要求
hearing some conversations if you want
听一些对话，如果你想
to share you can come up on stage
分享你可以上台
otherwise please keep it to yourself or
否则，请保密或
lead the room thank you
带领房间谢谢
you can customize records if you want to
您可以根据需要自定义记录
by adding adding some stuff for example
通过添加例如一些东西
you could if you want a different hash
如果您想要其他哈希，则可以
code algorithm than the one that's
代码算法比那个
provided you can write your own maybe
只要你可以自己写
you want to have the compute the norm
您想要计算标准
value of a point so you can you can add
点的价值，因此您可以添加
a norm method you can even provide your
您甚至可以提供一种规范方法
own constructor so you can do things
自己的构造函数，因此您可以做事
like insure invariance of data that's
像确保数据不变
coming in what you cannot do is add more
进入您无法做的事情就是增加更多
state you cannot add more data because
指出您无法添加更多数据，因为
that would violate the invariant that a
那会违反不变式
record is a transparent holder for data
记录是数据的透明持有者
so all of your data has to be declared
因此必须声明所有数据
upfront at the top
预先在顶部
another thing about records is that they
关于记录的另一件事是，它们
are immutable you cannot modify the
是一成不变的，你不能修改
value of a record object once it's been
记录对象的价值
created but that's ok if you really need
创建的，但是如果您真的需要可以
a immutable one one you can modify well
一个不变的人，你可以很好地修改
to just go write a class have your ID
只是去写一个有你的身份证的课程
write the class like like you always
像往常一样写课
have we do have a prototype
我们有原型吗
implementation of this but it's not in
的实现，但它不在
any early access build yet okay one one
任何早期访问版本，但还可以
last item from amber and then we'll move
琥珀色的最后一个项目，然后我们将移动
on suppose you have an object and it's
假设你有一个物体，它是
it's say it's gonna be an integer or a
就是说它将是一个整数或一个
double or a point the thing that we just
我们只是把事情加倍或一点
saw and you want to create a nice neat
看到，你想创造一个很好的整洁
little thing a formatted string that
小东西格式化字符串
that describes its value
描述其价值
you could write code like this format
你可以写这种格式的代码
method takes an object it initializes
方法接受一个它初始化的对象
our string s to unknown and we go
我们的字符串到未知，我们去
through if aab is instance of of an of
通过aab是的一个实例
an integer whoops sorry
整数不好意思
if i ABBA's instance of integer then we
如果我ABBA的整数实例，那么我们
cast
投
AAB to an integer we stick in a variable
AAB到一个整数，我们坚持一个变量
i and then we just ring that format of
我，然后我们按这种格式
our little message we do a similar thing
我们的小消息，我们做类似的事情
here if it's instance of double if it's
如果是double的实例，则为
in to the point you know then we extract
到你知道的地步，然后我们提取
pxpy we make our little string and
pxpy我们使我们的小字符串和
finally at the end we return s and it
最后，我们返回s
looks like I forgot a closing brace oh
好像我忘了一个大括号哦
no weird
不奇怪
okay pattern-matching lets us make this
好的模式匹配让我们做到这一点
more compact lets you express more
更紧凑，让您表达更多
clearly what you mean by doing this so
这样做显然意味着您的意思
what are highlighted in orange here are
橙色突出显示的是
things we called patterns a pattern
我们称之为模式的东西
combines combines two things it combines
结合结合两件事
a type and precondition test with a bind
具有绑定的类型和前提条件测试
operation if the test succeeds then it
如果测试成功，则进行操作
binds a variable and that variable is in
绑定一个变量，该变量位于
scope for the next bit of the of the if
if的下一位的范围
statement in this case so here's that
在这种情况下的声明，所以这是
your AAB instance of integer I if I if
您的整数I的AAB实例（如果存在）
AAB is an integer then it will be cast
AAB是一个整数，则将其强制转换
to an integer for you bound to I and
为您绑定到I和的整数
then you can just use I in that arm of
那你就可以用我
the if statement in the natural way you
自然的if语句，您
don't have to cast it yourself because
不必自己铸造，因为
well the compiler can figure this all
编译器可以很好地解决这一切
out for you what's really cool is you
为您服务真正酷的是您
can also use patterns to deconstruct
也可以使用模式来解构
things so a point has an X and a y we
东西，所以一个点有一个X，我们
saw that in the record declaration
在记录声明中看到了
previously if AB is an instance of
以前，如果AB是以下对象的实例
points then X then this will extract its
点然后X然后这将提取其
x and y values assign them to the
x和y值将它们分配给
variables x and y and then in the
变量x和y，然后在
remainder of this expression o mark mark
此表达式的其余部分o标记mark
mark pretend those aren't there
马克假装那些不在那里
I love Apple Keynote except for one
我爱Apple Keynote，除了一个
thing you can't extract code and and run
你无法提取代码并运行的东西
it and and test it in a natural way so I
并以自然的方式进行测试，所以我
apologize for the mistake on the slide
对幻灯片上的错误表示歉意
patterns play well with switch
模式与开关配合使用
expressions so we can bundle all this up
表达式，所以我们可以将所有这些捆绑在一起
up into a switch expression and this is
到一个开关表达式，这是
you much short much shorter than than it
你比它短得多
was much clearer and much less
更清晰，更少
boilerplate okay so that's a selection
样板好，所以这是一个选择
of features from amber let's now move on
琥珀色的功能现在让我们继续
to something completely different and
完全不同的东西
loom continuations and fibers can we
织机的延续和纤维
switch to this machine please it's the
切换到这台机器，这是
same slide so sorry milk might be okay
同样的幻灯片，所以对不起牛奶可能还可以
good we've got the right machine all
好，我们都有合适的机器
right so what is loom all about let's
对，那么织机到底是什么呢？
just look at some code
只是看一些代码
[Music]
[音乐]
so here I have a two day old build of
所以在这里我有两天大的建筑
the Loom repository from OpenJDK built
从OpenJDK构建的Loom存储库
district just a couple of days ago let's
几天前的地区
pop in the J shell and poke around a bit
弹出J shell并戳一下
so fibers are are addressed at the
因此纤维在
expense at the cost of threads threads
以线程为代价的开销
are great they've you know they've been
太好了，他们知道你去过
great for Java one of them one of the
对Java来说很重要，其中之一
things that Java kind of mean is snuck
Java那种卑鄙的东西
into to to more popular styles of
成为更流行的风格
computing is is is threads lots of
计算是线程很多
people need two threads they didn't that
人们需要两条线，不是
didn't necessarily know they needed them
不一定知道他们需要他们
but they but they did and Java brought
但他们却做到了，Java带来了
threads to a lot of people in a way that
与许多人互动的方式
was that was easy fairly easy to
那很容易
understand so we we can make a thread
了解，所以我们可以做一个线程
new thread
新线程
I'll use a little lambda here do that
我会在这里使用一点lambda
we've got a thread we can run it what
我们有一个线程，我们可以运行它
happens prints hi hey you know and so
发生打印嗨，你知道吗
you know thread object that's really
你知道真正的线程对象
easy and of course you can have
简单，当然你可以拥有
thousands or millions of these and and
成千上万的这些和
it all kind of works but threads come
各种各样的作品，但线程来了
with a lot of baggage we asked J shell
带着很多行李我们问了J壳
well how much baggage does it have
好，它有多少行李
exactly a thread object has all these
正是一个线程对象拥有所有这些
methods now yes
方法现在是
a handful of these are inherited from
其中一些是从
java.lang object you're stuck with those
你被那些卡住的java.lang对象
but there's a bunch of stuff here that's
但是这里有很多东西
of somewhat questionable nature there's
有一些可疑的性质
their thread priorities which in most
他们的线程优先级在大多数情况下
implementations mean nothing
实现没有任何意义
there are thread groups which have
有些线程组具有
almost no uses at all and are a an
几乎没有用，是一个
extraneous abstraction unfortunately
不幸的是，无关的抽象
introduced in the early days that we
在我们早期介绍的
can't really get rid of threads have a
不能真正摆脱线程有一个
thing called a context class loader in
所谓的上下文类加载器
the in the pantheon of questionable if
万神殿中是否存在疑问
not bad design decisions from the early
从早期开始就做出不错的设计决策
days of Java context class loader is is
Java上下文类加载器的日子是
is on that list it's lower than
在该列表上的位置低于
serialization and it's lower the
序列化，它降低了
finalization but it sits on the list of
定案，但它位于
things we we kind of wish we we hadn't
我们希望我们没有的事情
done them most of all a Java thread
完成了大部分Java线程
corresponds to an operating system
对应于操作系统
thread that's convening
正在召集的主题
because it means the operating system
因为这意味着操作系统
does all the work but it means that Java
完成所有工作，但这意味着Java
threads are expensive to create it means
创建线程很昂贵，这意味着
that it's expensive to switch from one
从一个切换到昂贵
job one Java thread to another one
将一个Java线程处理到另一个
operating system thread to another it's
操作系统线程到另一个
typically thousands of instructions to
通常有数千条指令
switch from one thread to another that
从一个线程切换到另一个
can be a long time because they're so
可能会很长一段时间，因为他们是如此
heavyweight inexpensive in order to get
重量级的便宜以获得
high-performance people who write things
高绩效的人写东西
like web servers tend to go with it with
就像网络服务器倾向于
non-blocking i/o techniques or
非阻塞I / O技术或
asynchronous i/o techniques these are
异步I / O技术是
really hard techniques to use properly
很难正确使用的技巧
so you will find experts who are writing
所以你会发现正在写作的专家
web servers doing it but then the
网络服务器这样做，但随后
applications that they're serving
他们正在服务的应用程序
typically won't use non-blocking or
通常不会使用非阻塞或
asynchronous i/o they're just written in
异步I / O，它们只是被写入
the normal sequential way and so web
正常的顺序方式等等
servers you know server hardware winds
您知道的服务器服务器硬件风
up being under you under utilized
被你利用之下
because you've got all these things
因为你拥有所有这些东西
happening in threads and there's no way
发生在线程中，没有办法
to make them more efficient so a fiber
使它们更有效率，所以纤维
as as the name suggests is a lightweight
顾名思义是轻巧的
thread let's make ourselves a fiber a
线让我们自己成为纤维
week and say fiber dot schedule I'll do
周说纤维点计划我会做
print one
打印一个
and so one difference in the API is with
因此，API的一个区别是
with fibers you create them and they're
用纤维创建它们，它们是
scheduled to run immediately so it
计划立即运行，因此
prints high and then it comes back and
打印高，然后又回来
prints the value of the the fiber object
打印纤维对象的值
and it's jus string notes has no carrier
而且它的字符串注释没有载体
threat what that means is right now this
威胁这意味着什么现在
fiber is not associated with a carrier
光纤与载体无关
thread you could have a fiber that does
线程，你可以有一个光纤
some computation than you some
一些计算比你一些
computation it's bound to a thread for
计算它绑定到一个线程
that time then it yields and if you
那时，它会产生，如果你
examined it and that's asked its asked
检查了它，这是问它的问题
for its to string it would say no
对于它的字符串会说不
carrier thread and then when it's
载体线程，然后在什么时候
running again it would say carrier
再次运行它会说载体
thread and give you the ID of the thread
线程并给您线程ID
so fibers allow the Java Runtime to
因此光纤允许Java Runtime
dynamically are dynamically map your
动态地动态映射您的
workload to operating system threads as
操作系统线程的工作负载为
you go because the switching between
你去，因为之间的切换
fibers is all done by the Java Runtime
纤维全部由Java Runtime完成
system switching between fibers can be
光纤之间的系统切换可以
done in at in a hundred or 200
在一百或200完成
instructions it's really really fast and
指示，它真的非常快，
fibers themselves are much smaller
纤维本身要小得多
objects a Java thread has comes not only
Java线程不仅具有对象
with a kind of biggest Java heap object
一个最大的Java堆对象
but there's also a thread stack
但也有一个线程堆栈
allocated out of heap that I think you
我认为你是从堆中分配出来的
know by default is like a megabyte or
默认情况下知道是兆字节还是
something so so that's big a fiber and
因此，这是一个很大的纤维，
the prototype implementation is on the
原型实现在
order of hundreds of bytes so if you
几百个字节的顺序，所以如果您
want to have a million fibers in your
想要拥有一百万根纤维
Java heap it's not a problem
Java堆不是问题
fibers are also simpler than threads
纤维也比线还简单
here all the methods on on our little
这里所有的方法都在我们的小
fibre object aside from the ones that
除了那些
you get it from java.lang object key
你从java.lang对象键中得到它
what can you do well you can you can
你能做好什么就可以
can't you can cancel a fiber you can ask
你不能取消你可以问的光纤吗
of a fibers alive you can ask if it's
活着的纤维中，您可以询问是否
been canceled you can await for deferred
被取消，您可以等待推迟
to terminate and and not much else so
终止，没有什么其他的
let's look at a more real example drop
让我们看一个更真实的例子
into my favorite IDE namely Emacs job
进入我最喜欢的IDE，即Emacs工作
whoops I did do a little benchmarking
我确实做了一些基准测试
here with a hypothetical rest service so
这里有一个假设的休息服务
this is using jax-rs and answering on
这是使用jax-rs并回答
the path rest we have a little method
剩下的路我们有一点方法
called sleep it takes a parameter number
称为sleep，它需要一个参数编号
of milliseconds you give it some
几毫秒，你就给它一些
milliseconds or it defaults to 100
毫秒或默认为100
and what does it do well it sleeps 400
睡得好吗400
milliseconds so it's this is just a a
毫秒，这就是一个
very simple simulation of a web service
Web服务的非常简单的模拟
that is written sequentially it does
那是顺序写的
something for a hundred milliseconds
一百毫秒
there's no non-blocking area synchronous
没有非阻塞区域同步
i/o going on here so let's run this with
我在这里继续，所以我们用
threads make threads bundled up into a
线程使线程捆绑成一个
make file we run maven of course so
制作文件，我们当然会运行Maven
there's running inside the jetty
码头里面跑来跑去
embedded web server and I'm using the
嵌入式Web服务器，我正在使用
Vegeta load a generation tool to hit
Vegeta加载生成工具以点击
that web server at a thousand requests
该Web服务器收到一千个请求
per second first day for a five-second
每秒第一天持续五秒钟
warm-up and then a ten-second run and
预热，然后运行十秒钟，然后
we'll look at a graph when it's finished
我们看完后的图表
there we go
我们去
oh yeah Firefox are difficut problem
哦，是的Firefox很难解决
thank you very much demo okay here our
非常感谢您的演示，好吧，我们的
response times for that sleep service
该睡眠服务的响应时间
with threads starts out well maybe not
与线程开始很好，也许不是
too bad okay yeah 300 millisecond
太差了，好吗300毫秒
latency 400 milliseconds service not
延迟400毫秒服务未
great but you see after the system's
很好，但是您会在系统的
been running for a while it gets gets
已经运行了一段时间了
really bad out here with you know
真的很糟糕，你知道
response times South a second a second
响应时间南一秒一秒
and a half in some cases this is not
在某些情况下这不是
what you want to see in production so
您想在生产中看到什么
let's reset that cool thing about jetty
让我们重置关于码头的酷事
is you configure it not with a pile of
你配置它不是一堆
XML or JSON or whatever you configure it
XML或JSON或您配置的任何内容
by writing Java code and we can
通过编写Java代码，我们可以
configure it to use threads simply by
配置它以简单地使用线程
giving it a custom thread pool so it has
给它一个自定义的线程池，所以它有
its own its own little thread pool
自己的小线程池
abstraction and all we need to do is go
抽象，我们要做的就是走
down here and override the execute
在这里并覆盖执行
method which by default will create a
默认情况下将创建一个方法
new thread and run it and instead we're
新线程并运行它，相反，我们是
just going to execute whatever needs to
只是要执行任何需要执行的操作
be executed on a fiber and let's see how
在光纤上执行，让我们看看如何
that goes
这些都不在了
so no actual change to the code just
所以对代码没有实际的改变
just went one change to a command-line
刚刚对命令行进行了一次更改
option and okay it didn't crash looks
选项，好吧，它没有崩溃
like good let's reload that and you see
很好，让我们重新加载它，您会看到
the fibers are actually doing pretty
纤维实际上做得很漂亮
well so there is an initial warmup
好，所以有一个初步的热身
period I'll zoom in on this segment
期间，我将放大此部分
there is an initial warmup period well
有一个初步的预热期
that you know the code gets compiled and
您知道代码已被编译，
you know hotspot does it's dynamic
你知道热点是动态的吗
compilation thing but after after it's
编译的东西，但是之后
been running for a while that latency
延迟了一段时间
goes down to usually just barely over
下降到通常刚刚结束
100 milliseconds so almost all of the
100毫秒，因此几乎所有
latency is taken up by that sleep and
延迟由该睡眠占用，
the overhead of switching from from one
从一个切换到另一个的开销
fiber to another is hard to measure
光纤到另一个很难测量
I mean it's showing up there but it's
我的意思是它在那里出现，但是
it's it's far less certainly than it was
它比以前要不确定得多
with threads so that's a big improvement
使用线程，因此有很大的改进
fibers are not just for avoiding
纤维不只是为了避免
non-blocking i/o although they're you
非阻塞的I / O，尽管他们是你
know there's obviously obviously very
知道显然很明显
good for that they opened the door to a
他们打开了通往
bun to a bunch of new techniques and
发to一堆新技术，
things like channels and data flow and
诸如渠道和数据流之类的东西
actors and the cool thing is these are
演员，最酷的是
all you can these will all be
所有这些你都可以
implementable as libraries on top of the
可作为库实现
Java platform you know they're not
您知道它们不是Java平台
things that we actually have to engineer
我们实际需要设计的东西
into the JVM into the language whatever
进入JVM进入语言
in past thing I did mention
过去我确实提到
continuations continuations are the
延续是
lower-level JVM mechanism upon which
较低级别的JVM机制
fibres are built continuations are
纤维是建立的延续
useful for a bunch of other things like
对于很多其他事情有用
generators with yield and so forth that
发电机的产量等等
we we might exploit in the future but
我们将来可能会利用，但
but we'll see and for now continuations
但我们会看到并且现在继续
probably won't it could be exposed in
可能不会暴露在
the public API but they are another
公共API，但它们是另一个
example of java borrowing
Java借用示例
well-established concepts from other
公认的概念
languages ok let's move on to Panama so
语言确定，让我们继续前往巴拿马，
invoking native code in Java how many
用Java调用本机代码
people I've actually written j'ni ok a
我实际上写过的人，好吧，
fair number how many people enjoyed it
公平的数字有多少人喜欢
okay good me neither it's it's it's kind
好吧，我也不是，这是一种
of painful
痛苦的
invoking native code interacting with
调用与之交互的本机代码
native data is is a pretty clunky thing
本机数据是一件很笨拙的事情
in in Java J&amp;I is is painful to write
用Java编写J＆I很难
it's it's slow to boot
开机很慢
I mean it's slow to run slow
我的意思是慢跑慢
additionally you have to write C code
另外，您必须编写C代码
compile it into a native library load
编译成本地库负载
the library and all that for native data
库以及用于本机数据的所有内容
you can use j'ni or you can use direct
您可以使用j'ni或直接使用
byte buffers but you know those get kind
字节缓冲区，但您知道它们会变种
of clunky too with any sort of
有点笨拙
sophisticated data format Panama is a is
巴拿马的复杂数据格式是
a brand-new for Java approach to
一种全新的Java方法
interacting with foreign functions and
与外部功能进行交互
foreign data again you know this is not
再次国外数据，你知道这不是
high level this is not a new idea other
高层次这不是一个新主意
platforms have certainly done this sort
平台当然做到了这种
of thing but now we're now we're trying
的事情，但现在我们正在尝试
to do it
去做吧
for for Java so let's take a look at
for Java，让我们看一下
some code
一些代码
here I've got another two-day-old build
在这里，我还有另外两天的时间
of the Panama repo so canonical demo of
巴拿马回购交易的典范演示
native native interaction is let's look
让我们来看看本地交互
at standard UNIX library call getpid get
在标准UNIX库调用getpid get
your process identifier really simple it
您的进程标识符真的很简单
takes no takes no arguments and it
不带不带参数，它
returns a bid T which is really just in
返回实际上是在的出价T
just an int and that is that is your
只是一个整数，那就是你的
process ID how hard can it be
进程ID有多难
to do this from Java well with J&amp;I you
用J＆I从Java很好地做到这一点
have to write a bunch of stuff and it's
必须写一堆东西，这是
all boilerplate e and ugly and easy to
所有样板都很丑陋，易于
get wrong let me show how you do it I'll
弄错了，让我告诉你你将如何做
show you how you do it in Panama so
告诉你如何在巴拿马做
panama has has three components one is a
巴拿马有三个组成部分，一个是
tool called J extract of memory at you
称为J的内存提取工具
from that from the main page we we
从主页上的我们
learned that to use this you need to
得知要使用此功能，您需要
look at you know standard H that header
看你知道标准H那个头
file and some stands of stuff in sis
文件和一些东西在sis
types dot H that that's effectively the
键入点H，这实际上是
the API definite definition here so what
API的定义在这里是什么
we can do is we can type J extract user
我们可以做的就是我们可以输入J提取用户
include you know standard data at dead
包括您知道的标准数据
age since it's a prototype I have to do
年龄，因为这是我必须要做的原型
this
这个
depayne no attention to the man behind
不关心背后的人
the option here and I'm gonna generate
这里的选项，我将生成
some classes from it so from you know
从中有些课，所以你知道
standard age we're going to get a bunch
标准年龄，我们将得到一堆
of Java classes they're actually all
实际上是所有的Java类
interfaces these are our compiled using
这些是我们使用的编译接口
the IV the LLVM front-end these are
IV LLVM前端这些是
these are compiled from the app those
这些是从应用程序编译的
actual c header files into a a java
实际的c头文件转换为aa java
representation of what's inside and if
里面是什么的表示，如果
we look inside one of these in
我们在其中之一中寻找
particular if we look inside in a
特别是如果我们看里面
standard underscore age class we see Oh
标准下划线年龄段我们看哦
familiar looking stuff all this all
所有这些看起来很熟悉的东西
these int constants that defined in you
您定义的这些int常量
know standard H it is an interface of
知道标准H是它的接口
these really are constants and abstract
这些真的是常量和抽象
shows up just because Java P is being as
出现是因为Java P被当作
as correct as it possibly can be we go
我们尽可能地正确
through here and look and we find oh
通过这里，看看，我们找到了哦
look there's get pip so we have an
看起来有点子，所以我们有一个
interface here that was generated from
从此处生成的界面
the C header
C头
what are we gonna do with it well at
我们该如何做好呢
run-time what we're going to do is
运行时我们要做的是
import it we're going to we're going to
导入它，我们要去
import the Panama API which is what most
导入巴拿马API，这是大多数
of it is a Java API that models see data
它是一个Java API，模型可以查看数据
types so ad you know there's a pointer
类型，以便广告您知道有一个指针
type in there and it's parameterised and
在那里输入并进行参数化，
other memory look at memory looking
其他记忆看记忆看
things to get to get the process ID we
获得流程ID的事情
will invoke invoke a static method in
将调用调用静态方法
the Panama libraries class to do a
巴拿马图书馆上课
binding what that binding does is you're
绑定所做的绑定是你
saying okay I've got this unit standard
说好，我已经有了这个单位的标准
underscore H interface that represents
下划线代表的H接口
the the UNIX library thing I went to
我去过的UNIX库
invoke I pass it a a method handle
调用我将其传递给方法句柄
lookup object for my current execution
我当前执行的查找对象
context and what I get back is an object
上下文，我得到的是一个对象
that implements that unit standard H
实施该单元标准H
interface and inside that object is a
接口，在该对象内部是一个
getpid method which I can invoke and
我可以调用的getpid方法
just for sanity's sake I will also
为了理智我也会
invoke the java api that we already have
调用我们已经拥有的Java API
the returns to get paid method so let me
获得报酬方法的回报，让我
just run this classes get hid java no
只需运行此类即可隐藏Java否
I'm not compiling this because we can
我没有编译这个，因为我们可以
now launch single file source code
现在启动单个文件源代码
programs I've needed directly at the
我直接需要的程序
runtime with the runtime we run this it
运行时与运行时我们运行它
does its thing
尽其所能
and it gets the process ID and I never
它获取进程ID，而我从不
actually had to look at any C code I
实际上不得不看我的任何C代码
never had to write any C code I didn't
从来没有写任何我没有的C代码
need to compile a dot iso file and
需要编译一个点iso文件，然后
remember where it was and tell java how
记住它在哪里，并告诉java如何
to find it so that's that that's the
找到它，就是这样
quickie demo of panama thing to say
巴拿马的快速演示示范
about panama is it is everybody will
关于巴拿马，是每个人都会
benefit from it but most people will
从中受益，但大多数人会
benefit from it indirectly it's really
间接受益于它
meant at the it's really meant to be
的意思是真的
used by people who maintain native
由维护本地语言的人使用
libraries so for example people who
图书馆，例如
maintain things like OpenGL or
维护诸如OpenGL或
tensorflow
张量流
you know they're experts in how those
你知道他们是那些专家
libraries work they can use panama - you
图书馆可以使用巴拿马的工作-您
know digest their own c c++ header files
知道摘要自己的c c ++头文件
and provide to you an easy - easy to use
并为您提供易于使用的
java api that it was not derived from
并非源自的Java API
those
那些
files but the fact that they can use
文件，但他们可以使用的事实
that step makes their job much easier as
这一步使他们的工作变得更加轻松
task performance panama is currently
任务绩效巴拿马目前
slightly faster than j and i but we have
比j和i快一点，但是我们有
some code still in the works that's
一些代码仍在工作中
actually looking good it will probably
实际上看起来不错，可能会
be around four times faster in the end
最后快四倍
all right let's move on to the last item
好吧，让我们继续最后一项
valhalla value types and specialized
valhalla值类型和专用
generics why why are we working with
泛型为何与我们合作
working on Valhalla and we've been
在瓦尔哈拉（Valhalla）工作，我们一直在
working on Valhalla for a while now it
现在在瓦尔哈拉工作了一段时间
is a big project making very very deep
这是一个非常深远的大项目
cuts in but in both the language and the
切入但在语言和语言上
virtual machine well the answer in one
虚拟机将答案合而为一
image is this today's processors are
图像是今天的处理器
vastly different from those we had in
与我们所经历的大不相同
1995 when drop 1 Java was a new thing
1995年，Java 1下降是新事物
the cost of a CASP cache miss has
CASP缓存未命中的代价是
increased from between a factor of 200
从200倍增加
to a factor of a thousand it can now
现在可以达到一千倍
take forever if - if I memory access
如果-如果我记忆访问，请永远使用
miss misses in the cache why is this
错过缓存中的错过原因
relevant to Java well being an
与Java健康相关
object-oriented language we have lots of
面向对象的语言，我们有很多
objects around if it's not a primitive
不是原始对象的对象
type then it's an object if you have
如果有的话，那就是一个对象
objects then you have pointers and
对象，那么你有指针和
objects point off to other objects and
物体指向其他物体
every time you chase a pointer that's an
每次您追逐一个指针
opportunity to take a cache miss miss
抓住机会错过小姐
and have your processor sit there for
并让您的处理器坐在那里
hundreds thousands of cycles waiting for
等待数十万个周期
the slow pokey memory system to return
缓慢的pokey记忆系统返回
some data
一些数据
another thing about objects is is
关于对象的另一件事是
obvious objects are heavyweight every
每个明显的物体都很重
object has effects that have identity
对象具有具有标识的效果
you can synchronize on any object and
您可以在任何对象上同步
people do this I've you know I've seen
人们这样做我知道你已经知道
the industrial applications where where
工业应用在哪里
people were synchronizing on the string
人们在弦上同步
constant Y Capital y and they had
常数Y资本y并且他们有
gazillions of these string constant Y's
这些字符串常数Y的兆亿
that they were synchronizing them really
他们真的在同步他们
anyway so this gets really painful
无论如何，所以这真的很痛苦
especially when you're dealing with a
特别是当您处理
lot of data as you might be in the
您可能会在其中存储大量数据
machine
机
you're trying trying to do image
你正在尝试做形象
processing or something so we're trying
处理之类的，所以我们正在尝试
to address that and and we think the
解决这个问题，我们认为
missing abstraction here is is value
缺少抽象是价值
types in Java there's no way to declare
Java中的类型无法声明
a pure data aggregator I'm sure I've
我确定我是一个纯粹的数据聚合器
showed your records records are pure in
显示您的记录是纯记录
a sense but they still wind up being
从某种意义上讲，但他们仍然被
objects right what we want is a way to
正确的对象是我们想要的一种方法
say here's here's a thing it's it's it's
说这是这件事，是
just data there's no there's no state
只是数据，就没有状态
it'll never change it doesn't need
它永远不会改变，不需要
you're never gonna synchronize on it it
你永远不会同步它
doesn't need to be in the heap if you
如果您不需要在堆中
can allocate it and registers for its
可以分配它并为其注册
entire lifetime do that right now we we
整个一生都在做，现在我们
we can't do that
我们不能那样做
as John Rose likes to say if we do this
就像约翰·罗斯（John Rose）喜欢说如果我们这样做
right you you it'll you'll be able to
对你，你将能够
code it like a class but it'll work like
像一个类一样编码，但它将像
an int so that's that's where we're
一个整数，那就是我们所在的地方
trying to go with valhalla let's switch
尝试和瓦尔哈拉一起去让我们切换
to Baja demo here's the version yep
到Baja演示这里是版本
that's the right one
那是正确的
and once again let's look a little code
再一次让我们看一些代码
here complex numbers kind of like points
这里复数有点像点
the same idea right that's good it could
同样的想法对，这可能很好
be records in some future version yet
被记录在将来的版本中
public class complex you've got real and
你有真实的公共课堂复合体
imaginary you've got a constructor
想象中你有一个构造函数
you've got accessors and you've got
你有访问者，你有
added multiply if you can if you're in
如果可以的话，添加倍数
benchmark mode you have complex numbers
基准模式，您有复数
what what how do you benchmark them you
你怎样对他们进行基准测试
multiply matrices yes of course
乘矩阵当然是
perfectly natural operation so we're
完全自然的操作，所以我们
gonna do some matrix multiplication here
要在这里做一些矩阵乘法
I've said it set up a set this up as a
我已经说过将它设置为
benchmark using Lexi ship lives very
使用Lexi船的基准生活非常
fine a job on micro benchmark harness so
在微基准测试线束上做得很好
there are some annotations here telling
这里有一些注释
it how to run it we have two complex
它如何运行我们有两个复杂
matrices represented as arrays of arrays
表示为数组数组的矩阵
of complex objects we populate it with
复杂对象的填充
some random numbers that we set things
一些我们设定事物的随机数
up and then of course we have them it's
然后我们当然有他们
a matrix multiplication itself standard
矩阵乘法本身的标准
cubic algorithm walker crossing of the
的三次算法沃克穿越
rows of one matrix columns another do
一个矩阵列的行另一列
the point-wise
明智的
applications and sums and boom you get a
应用程序和总和和繁荣你会得到一个
result okay let's run this may even mix
结果好吧，让我们运行它甚至可以混合
another guest appearance okay so I'm
另一个客人的样子还可以，所以我
going to do three three warmups
要做三三个热身
warm up warm up iterations here and then
预热，然后再预热
some actual test runs and this is taking
一些实际的测试运行，这正在
about four seconds per matrix multiply
每个矩阵约四秒钟
and my laptop is not getting worm or
而且我的笔记本电脑没有蠕虫或
really working very hard at all
真的很努力
iteration one yeah about for about four
迭代一是的大约四
seconds per matrix multiply if you look
每个矩阵的秒数乘以
at the GC alec rate norm that's how much
在GC alec率标准下，这是多少
Alec how much memory is being allocated
Alec正在分配多少内存
per multiplication and that's almost
每个乘法，几乎
four megabytes just a multiply a couple
四兆字节乘以一对
of 500 by 500 matrices and that's not
500 x 500矩阵，那不是
very impressive okay that's that's a
非常令人印象深刻的是
little hairy let's look at it and Emax
小毛茸茸的让我们看看它和Emax
okay we have this morning from Alexi pay
好吧，今天早上我们有Alexi pay
attention to that advice it's very good
注意那个建议非常好
advice multiply is taking almost four
建议乘以几乎四
seconds each each round we just mark
我们每圈标记秒数
that we're allocating about four
我们分配了大约四个
gigabytes for each one and then another
每个千兆字节然后另一个
interesting metric here which all
这里所有的有趣指标
highlight is the instructions per cycle
重点是每个周期的指令
so the processor in this laptop is is
所以这台笔记本电脑的处理器是
asked I asked until skylake processor
问我问，直到Skylake处理器
it's capable of retiring four
它有能力退休四个
instructions per CPU cycle it is
每个CPU周期的指令是
retiring me barely more than one so
退休我几乎不止一个
that's this number is telling us that
就是这个数字告诉我们
the processor is mostly just sitting
处理器通常只是坐着
around twiddling its thumbs waiting for
左右摇动拇指等待
the memory system because it's chasing
内存系统，因为它正在追逐
pointers from from those those arrays
来自那些数组的指针
and the matrices off to all the complex
和所有复杂的矩阵
number objects and of course I had to
数字对象，当然我必须
allocate a bunch of complex number
分配一堆复数
objects because every complex number is
对象，因为每个复数都是
an object cuz oh it's object-oriented
一个对象，因为它是面向对象的
everything is an object great well not
一切都很好，不是
really as we're seeing now so what we're
就像我们现在看到的那样
gonna do is I'll go into this complex
我要做的是进入这个综合体
class and I'm going to add one key word
课，我要添加一个关键词
we
我们
II gonna make this a value class which
我将把它作为一个价值类
looks like a class but works more like
看起来像一堂课，但更像
an int and let's run our benchmark again
一个int，让我们再次运行基准
they recompile it since I change the
他们重新编译它，因为我改变了
source we do some warm-ups though it's
来源，尽管我们做一些热身
taking 366 milliseconds per operation so
每次操作需要366毫秒
that's that's quite a bit faster cool I
那是相当快的酷我
did this talk six weeks ago and it was
这是六个星期前的演讲，当时
faster than that so Amy this is like
比那快，所以艾米就像
this is live prototype code it changes
这是它的实时原型代码
everyday and we're allocating only about
每天，我们只分配
four megabytes not gigabytes for
四兆字节而不是千兆字节
megabytes for matrix multiply because
矩阵乘以兆字节是因为
we're the only allocations happening is
我们是唯一正在发生的分配是
for is for the result matrix we're not
对于结果矩阵，我们不是
having to allocate a bunch of
不得不分配一堆
intermediate complex number objects as
中间复数对象为
we go so let's go back into Emacs for
我们走了，让我们回到Emacs
comparison I'll put the old numbers at
比较，我将旧数字放在
the top and load this in at the bottom
顶部并在底部加载
okay new results at the bottom 338
好的底部338个新结果
milliseconds per operation if we do a
如果执行一次操作，则每个操作的毫秒数
little quick division here that's it's
小小的快速划分就是这样
about 11 times faster than the other
比其他快11倍
version it's allocating a lot a lot less
版本分配的少很多
and instructions per cycle its retiring
和每个周期的退役说明
almost three so it's making much better
差不多三个，所以做得更好
use of the processor you know for four
使用您知道的四个处理器
would be ideal being able to do almost
几乎可以做到的理想
three is certainly way better than
三当然比
barely more than one so that's a quick
几乎不止一个，所以很快
look at Valhalla and value classes even
看瓦尔哈拉和价值类，甚至
once Valhalla is done even if you never
一旦瓦尔哈拉完成，即使你从来没有
use it you will benefit from it because
使用它，您会从中受益，因为
Valhalla will enable people who write
瓦尔哈拉将使写作的人
libraries not not just like the
图书馆不只是像
libraries in the JDK but people you
JDK中的库，但是您
people write libraries everywhere to
人们到处写库
redo their data structures to make them
重做它们的数据结构以使它们
much more efficient so everybody will
效率更高，所以每个人都会
benefit even if not everybody uses it
受益，即使不是每个人都使用它
directly alright so that was Valhalla
好吧，那是瓦尔哈拉
amber loom Panama Mahalo this is a
琥珀色的织机Panama Mahalo这是一个
really exciting time for Java
Java真正令人兴奋的时刻
our rnd pipeline is richer than it's
我们的rnd管道比它丰富
been in in many many years you know
你已经有很多年了
starting with lambda continuing with
以lambda开头，以
with with with jigsaw and now with these
与拼图一起，现在与这些
projects there's a really bright future
项目前途一片光明
ahead here I hope that you'll take a
在这里，我希望你会
look at some of the early access
看看一些抢先体验
releases send us feedback and and help
发布给我们反馈和帮助
us help us move Java forward if you'd
如果您愿意，我们可以帮助我们推动Java向前发展
like to take a look at the early access
喜欢看一下抢先体验
stuff it's all on JDK java.net right now
东西都在JDK java.net上了
we have EA builds 4:13 for Panama for
我们有EA为巴拿马建造了4:13的EA
Valhalla first up for some other things
瓦尔哈拉（Valhalla）首先要做其他事情
there I'm told there will be an early
有人告诉我会早
access build for loom probably in the
可能在
next month maybe a month or two months
下个月也许一个月或两个月
there are two minutes left for quick
还剩两分钟
questions otherwise you can catch me at
问题，否则你可以抓住我
the Oracle booth afterward or in the
甲骨文展位之后或之后
hallway whenever I'll be here today and
每当我今天在这里和
tomorrow yes sir three years long term
明天是先生三年
support releases are every three years
支持版本每三年发布一次
any other quick questions sir
先生，还有其他问题要问
yes values and records will work
是的，值和记录将起作用
together you will be able to type value
一起您将能够输入值
record complex real imaginary done okay
记录复杂的真实虚构就可以了
one minute race is on yes sir what the
一分钟的比赛即将结束，先生，
I'm sorry I can't hear you a future of
对不起，我听不到您的未来
future of threads well what's the future
线程的未来以及未来如何
of the classpath or we're ever gonna
类路径，否则我们将永远
take it up take it away no of course not
拿起拿走它当然不会
no threads they'll be there forever
没有线程，他们将永远在那里
but you know I think gradually we will
但是你知道我认为我们会逐渐
encourage people to migrate off of them
鼓励人们从他们那里迁移
there will be some big performance
会有一些大的表现
benefits to be gained by going through
通过经历获得的好处
that migration effort so you know
迁移工作，所以您知道
hopefully in the future people will not
希望将来人们不会
be writing in threads by default and by
默认情况下通过
the way with with a fiber Orion the
用纤维猎户座的方式
computation model the need for these
计算模型对这些的需求
complex reactive frameworks kind of goes
复杂的反应式框架
away so the little screen here is
离开，所以这里的小屏幕是
telling you time is up thank you very
告诉你时间到了，非常感谢
much
许多
oh and and and don't believe anything I
哦，还有，我什么都不相信
said
说过
[Applause]
[掌声]
[Music]
[音乐]